Guide to the Alumni Association Records 1888-2008
Oregon State University Libraries, University Archives
- Administrative Files, 1914-2008; Subgroup 2
  - Sound Recordings, 1949-1991; Series XIV
    - OSC vs. University of Oregon football game, 1949 (Box 6)
      4 reel-to-reel tapes
    - 1915 football team reunion, 1965 (Box 6)
      Also includes recreation of play-by-play for OAC vs Michigan Aggies 1915 football game; 2 reel-to-reel tapes.
    - What is Good About OSU, 1970 (Box 6)
      Speech by Fred Shideler to the Chamber of Commerce Forum; reel-to-reel tape.
    - Join the Orange Forces, 1981 (Box 6)
      Two copies of a 45 rpm sound disk of the football fight song. Lyrics are printed on the dust jacket.
    - Songs of Oregon State College, circa 1950 (Box 6)
      Two sets of two 78 rpm sound disks produced by the Oregon State College Alumni Association, the Music Department and the KOAC radio station. It includes a recording of the Oregon State Creed with words by E.T. Reed and music by Joseph Brye, sung by the Oregon State College A Cappella Choir (directed by Robert Walls). The set also includes Hail to Old OSC sung by the Oregon State College Choir Men and the Alma Mater sung by the Oregon State College Choir. Listening copy available on CD and on online in Best of the Archives digital collection.
    - Songs at Oregon State College - Within a Vale of Western Mountains, circa 1953 (Box 7)
      Four sets of three 78 rpm sound disks produced by the Oregon State College Alumni Association include recordings of the Oregon State College Band and Glee Club performing the OSC Medley, Indiana State Band (March), the Alma Mater, Roadways, Mighty Beavers, Storm King, Hail to Old OSC, Toast to the Team, and March of the Spanish Soldiery. A 33 1/3 rpm edition (1 disk) is also included. Listening copy available on CD and online in Best of the Archives digital collection.
  - Scrapbook, 1950-1951; Series XV (Box 13)
    Alumni Association publicity and promotional projects, clippings about activities, direct mail efforts, and other projects for the period June 1950 through June 1951. Includes clippings; ephemera; copies of mailings; and issues of the alumni magazine.
  - List of Alumni, undated; Series XVI (Box 5)
    Typewritten list of alumni by class year for Classes of 1870 through 1925; indicates if individual is deceased. The list is undated but may have been prepared in the 1950s or early 1960s.
  - Academy of Lifelong Learning, 2008; Series XVII (Box 5)
    Schedule of classes for spring 2008.
- Publications, 1929-2005; Subgroup 3
  Subgroup 3 consists of records that document the major publications of the Association, the alumni magazine and the alumni directory, as well as the Orange and Black and OSU Scope. Copies of the Orange and Black and the alumni directories are included with these records. Copies of the alumni magazine and OSU Scope are maintained as separate collections.
  - Alumni Magazine, 1929-1998; Series I
    The Alumni Magazine series consists of materials documenting the preparation and distribution of the Association's alumni magazine, the OAC Alumnus, Oregon State Monthly, and Oregon Stater. The records include extensive subject files on prominent alumni, faculty and staff, and special events; letters to the editor; and editorial materials for individual issues. The letters to the editor include letters and photocopies of diaries and family histories sent by alumni who are descendants of Oregon Trial pioneers. Information from the letters was used in a December 1992 Oregon Stater article commemorating the 150th anniversary of the Oregon Trail.
    - Indexes, 1929-1979 (Box 5)
      Includes indexes for the 1929-1933 and 1976-1979 issues of the alumni magazine.
    - Subject Files
      - Alumni, 1944-1993; 4 folders (Box 5)
      - Andrus, Governor Cecil D., 1973-1981 (Box 5)
      - "Books for Birmingham" campaign, 1989 (Box 5)
      - Byrne, John V., 1981-1984 (Box 5)
      - CH2M Hill, 1966-1986 (Box 5)
      - Edwards, Webley, 1960-1977 (Box 5)
      - Englebart, Douglas C., 1986-1987 (Box 5)
      - Faculty, 1970-1986 (Box 5)
      - Fagans, J. Kenneth, 1972-1975 (Box 5)
      - Giustina, N.B. (Nat), 1983 (Box 5)
      - Harris, Milton, 1970-1984 (Box 5)
      - Homecoming, 1979-1985 (Box 5)
      - Jackson, Glenn, 1977-1980 (Box 5)
      - Johnson, Bill ('30), stories and reminiscences, ca. 1995 (Box 5)
      - Lemon, E.B. Distinguished Alumni Award, 1978-1986 (Box 5)
      - MacVicar, Robert W., 1970-1976 (Box 5)
      - Obituaries, 1966-1986 (Box 5)
      - Open Meetings Law, 1975-1981 (Box 5)
      - Oregon Trail Project, 1992 (Box 5)
      - Parker, Charles T., 1972-1977 (Box 5)
      - Pauling, Linus, 1954-1986 (Box 5)
      - Pauling Memorial Publication, 1994 (Box 5)
      - Poling, Dan, 1998 (Box 5)
      - Prefontaine and Ebba, 1997 (Box 5)
        Track athletes at University of Oregon and OSU.
      - Robertson, Bill ("Ropes"), 1980 (Box 5)
      - Starker, T.J., 1962-1983 (Box 5)
      - Stewart, L.L. "Stub", 1975-1976 (Box 5)
      - Student Life in the Past, undated (Box 5)
      - Trysting Tree, 1983 (Box 5)
    - Subject Files (Accession 2000:087), circa 1895-1984
      Subject files compiled for research purposes by the staff of the Oregon Stater alumni magazine. The files pertain to OSU alumni, homecoming celebrations, commencement and graduation ceremonies, and reunions. The files include photographs, newspaper clippings, magazines (especially copies of the Stater), minutes, and correspondence.
      - A -- Important OSU Alumni (Box 17)
      - Baker, Harry (Box 17)
      - Baker, Terry Wayne (Box 17)
      - Bancroft, Vivian (Box 17)
      - Bandy, Orville (Box 17)
      - Barber, Rex (Box 17)
      - Barnes, John M. (Box 17)
      - Barratt, Jim (Box 17)
      - Bartel, Erv (Box 17)
      - Bartholomew, Frank (Box 17)
      - Batcheller, Oliver (Box 17)
      - Bates, Albert (Box 17)
      - Bates, Mercedes (Box 17)
      - Bauer, Albert (Box 17)
      - Bauer, Bruce (Box 17)
      - Bauer, Walter (Box 17)
      - Baughman, Fred (Box 17)
      - Baum, David (Box 17)
      - Baum, Robert (Box 17)
      - Beamer, Clarence (Box 17)
      - Bean, Bruce (Box 17)
      - Beck, Larry (Box 17)
      - Beck, James (Box 17)
      - Bell, John (Box 17)
      - Bell, Sam (Box 17)
      - Belton, Howard (Box 17)
      - Bennett, Ralph (Box 17)
      - Bennett, William (Box 17)
      - Benson, B.F. (Box 17)
      - Bertsch, Howard (Box 17)
      - Birkie, William (Box 17)
      - Blair, Dean (Box 17)
      - Blakely, Jud (Box 17)
      - Blakely, Mrs. Martin (Frieda Linder) (Box 17)
      - Blitz, William (Box 17)
      - Bohren, A.K. (Box 17)
      - Bothwell, Lindley (Box 17)
      - Brandis, John (Box 17)
      - Breese, Mel (Box 17)
      - Bregger, John (Box 17)
      - Briggs, John (Box 17)
      - Briggs, Mark (Box 17)
      - Brodie, Renton K. (Box 17)
      - Broten, George Arthur (Box 17)
      - Brown, Delmar (Box 17)
      - Brown, Mr. and Mrs. Richard (Box 17)
      - Brown, Robert (Box 17)
      - Brumfield, Kirby (Box 17)
      - Bruns, George (Box 17)
      - Byrne, John "Jack" (Box 17)
      - Byrne, John V. (Box 17)
      - Carl, Irene (Box 17)
      - Carl, Marion (Box 17)
      - Carlson, John (Box 17)
      - Carpenter, Ken (Box 17)
      - Carter, Lloyd (Box 17)
      - Carter, M. Joe (Box 17)
      - Casey, Kathleen (Box 17)
      - Cheldelin, V. (Box 17)
      - Chiu, Arthur (Box 17)
      - Christiansen, C.C. (Box 17)
      - Clark, Herman (Box 17)
      - Clarke, Loyal (Box 17)
      - Class Reunions (Box 17)
      - Clement, Boyd (Box 17)
      - Cole, Leland (Box 17)
      - Coleman, Ralph (Box 17)
      - Collegemates (Collegemates Luncheon Gatherings) (Box 17)
      - Colvig, Vance DeBar (Pinto) (Box 17)
      - Conklin, Robert (Box 17)
      - Cook, John Earl (Box 17)
      - Cooper, Mrs. James A. (Grace Starr) (Box 17)
      - Corbett, O.W. (Box 17)
      - Cordial, Jim (Box 17)
      - Corso, Hope Chamberlin (Box 17)
      - Counts, Mel (Box 17)
      - Cowgill, Clara (Box 17)
      - Cowgill, Helen (Box 17)
      - Crandall, Cliff (Box 17)
      - Crawford, Thomas (Box 17)
      - Crimmins, Jerry (Box 17)
      - Cronemiller, Lynn F. (Box 17)
      - Cross Country (1961 NCAA Champions) (Box 17)
      - Cummings, Orville (Box 17)
      - Cutler, William (Box 17)
      - Davis, Donald (Box 17)
      - Davies, Henry (Box 17)
      - Day, Edgar Allen (Box 17)
      - Day, John (Box 17)
      - Dixon, James (Box 17)
      - DeBoest, Henry F. (Box 17)
      - Delzell, Thomas (Box 17)
      - Demith, Jimmy (Box 17)
      - DeSylvia, Tom (Box 17)
      - Dezendorf, Nelson (Box 17)
      - Dimick, Roland E. (Box 17)
      - Dodge, Ray (Box 17)
      - Dooley, Ed (Box 17)
      - Dorsey, Dean (Box 17)
      - Downie, Hal (Box 17)
      - Drew, Preston (Box 17)
      - Dudley, Darle W. (Box 17)
      - Durden, Don (Box 17)
      - Dybuik, Russell (Box 17)
      - Dyer, Joseph M. (Box 17)
      - Eaton, Robert (Box 17)
      - Ebeling, Dick W. (Box 17)
      - Eckman, Don (Box 17)
      - Edwards, M. Lowell (Wife-Margaret Watt) (Box 17)
      - Edwards, Webley (Box 17)
      - Eggers, Johnny (Box 17)
      - Elder, Terry B. (Box 17)
      - Eldredge, Don (Box 17)
      - Eldredge, Kenneth R. (Box 17)
      - Ellison, Vern (Box 17)
      - Emmett, Paul (Box 17)
      - Erickson, Minton (Box 17)
      - Ewalt, Robert (Box 17)
      - Exley, Jerry (Box 17)
      - Fenner, John (Box 17)
      - Finlay, Gordon (Box 17)
      - Fisher, Jim (Box 17)
      - Floberg, Ralph (Box 17)
      - Forde, Diane Lund (Box 17)
      - Foster, Lyle W. (Box 17)
      - Francis, Joe (Box 17)
      - Fugate, Raymond (Box 17)
      - Funk, Arnold (Box 17)
      - Gabrielson, Ira (Box 17)
      - Garland, Charles (Box 17)
      - Geary, Edward A. (Box 17)
      - Gellatly, John (Box 17)
      - General (Box 17)
      - Getty, Leonard C. (Box 17)
      - Gianella, Vincent P. (Box 17)
      - Gilkey, Richard (Box 17)
      - Gill, Amory (Box 17)
      - Gill, Harold (Box 17)
      - Gill, Slats (Box 17)
      - Gillet, Ira (Box 17)
      - Gillette, Dean (Box 17)
      - Gilley, R. Stevens (Box 17)
      - Giustina, N.B. (Box 17)
      - Godman, John (Box 17)
      - Goodall, Mrs. Kenneth (Mary Homes) (Box 17)
      - Gotta, Jack (Box 17)
      - Graduation Class Photos, circa 1890s (Box 17)
      - Graham, C.H. (Box 17)
      - Graham, Jackson (Box 17)
      - Gray, Gene (Box 17)
      - Gray, John (Box 17)
      - Grayson, Mark (Box 17)
      - Griffen (Dr.) (Box 17)
      - Griffen, Z. Wayne (Box 17)
      - Gross, Calvin E. (Box 17)
      - Grosz, Walter (Box 17)
      - Groves, Frank (Box 17)
      - Hageman, Leo (Box 17)
      - Hall, John H. (Box 17)
      - Halverson, William (Box 17)
      - Hamill, Robert (Box 17)
      - Hansen, Julia Butler (Box 17)
      - Hardie, Stewart (Box 17)
      - Harris, Milton (Box 17)
      - Hart, Frederick (Box 17)
      - Harvey, Morris (Box 17)
      - Hatfield Mark O. (U.S. Senator) (Box 17)
      - Hathaway, Mark (Box 17)
      - Hattan, Elton (Box 17)
      - Hawley, Norman (Box 17)
      - Hayes, Dalebert Edward (Box 17)
      - Hayner, C.T. (Box 17)
      - Hays, Donald (Box 17)
      - Head, J. Al (Box 17)
      - Head, S. Conrad (Box 17)
      - Hedges, Frank Robert (Box 17)
      - Helmer, Oscar M. (Box 17)
      - Henniger, Jean Floyd (Box 17)
      - Heywood, Eunice (Box 17)
      - Hildebrandt, Lou (Box 17)
      - Hill, D.D. (Box 17)
      - Hill, Fred (Box 17)
      - Hirstel, Bob (Box 17)
      - Hoffman, E. Neil (Box 17)
      - Hogan, Brooks (Box 17)
      - Holcomb, Glenn (Box 17)
      - Hollandsworth, Helen (Box 17)
      - Hollingsworth, Guilford (Box 17)
      - Holt, Mrs. Curtis (Isabella Downs) (Box 17)
      - Holt, Howard (Box 17)
      - Homecoming Materials, 1955-1969 (Box 17)
      - Hood, Gordon (Box 17)
      - Houghton, E.W. (Box 17)
      - Howie, George (Box 17)
      - Huggins, M.M. (Box 17)
      - Hughes, Henry (Box 17)
      - Hulsman, Helen (Mrs. Walter Kelly) (Box 17)
      - Humphrey, Lloyd (Box 17)
      - Hurd, Owen (Box 17)
      - Jackson, Glenn (Box 17)
      - Jarvis, Joe (Box 17)
      - Jenkins, Gay Harding (Box 17)
      - Jensen, James H. (Box 17)
      - Jewett, Leonard G. (Box 17)
      - Johnson, Alton (Box 17)
      - Johnson, Dick (Box 17)
      - Johnson, Hilbert (Box 17)
      - Johnson, Wilfred (Box 17)
      - Joy, Barnard (Box 17)
      - Joy, Clifford (Box 17)
      - Kallander, R.M. (Box 17)
      - Keema, Bud (Box 17)
      - Keene, Roy S. (Box 17)
      - Keep, Barney (Box 17)
      - Kerr, Robert Todd (Box 17)
      - Kerr, William Jasper (Box 17)
      - Kiefer, Harry J. (Box 17)
      - King, Jean (Box 17)
      - Kipper, Louis (Box 17)
      - Kirk, William (Box 17)
      - Kirkpatrick, H.L. (Box 17)
      - Kleinschmidt, Arthur (Box 17)
      - Knoll, Robert (Box 17)
      - Kofoid, Marvin (Box 17)
      - Lafferty, Chester (Box 17)
      - Lange, Kenneth (Box 17)
      - Laythe, Leo (Box 17)
      - Lear, Gene (Box 17)
      - Leihy, Charles Willard (Box 17)
      - Lemon, E.B. (Box 17)
      - Lewis, Ed (Box 17)
      - Lieuallen, Roy Elwayne (Box 17)
      - Lincoln, Richard (Box 17)
      - Lowden, Merle (Box 17)
      - Lowe, Paul (Box 17)
      - Lowry, Hugh R. (Box 17)
      - Lumm, Marjorie (Box 17)
      - Lundeen, Robert (Box 17)
      - Lundstron, A.A. (Box 17)
      - McCallister/Finley (5-generations at OSU) (Box 17)
      - McCollum, Charles (Box 17)
      - McCullough, John Price (Box 17)
      - McCullogh, Walter (Box 17)
      - McDaniel, Hobart (Box 17)
      - McKay, Douglas (Box 17)
      - McMicken, Craig (Box 17)
      - McMurdo, Scott (Box 17)
      - MacVicar, Robert (Box 17)
      - Madden, Sally (Box 17)
      - Mann, Dave (Box 17)
      - Maple, Howard (Box 17)
      - Maris, Homer (Box 17)
      - Maser, Clifford (Box 17)
      - Meechan, Charles (Box 17)
      - Meek, Fred (Box 18)
      - Memorial Union (Box 18)
      - Merryfield, Fred (Box 18)
      - Miller, Helen (Box 18)
      - Miller, Mark (Box 18)
      - Miller, Richard A. (Box 18)
      - Moeller, Therald (Box 18)
      - Moir, David (Box 18)
      - Moore, Harriet (Box 18)
      - Moore, Spencer (Box 18)
      - Morris, Homer (Box 18)
      - Morris, James (Box 18)
      - Morris, Walter (Box 18)
      - Mosby, David Clayton (Box 18)
      - Mulligan, Joe (Box 18)
      - Munford, Ken (Box 18)
      - Murphy, Donald (Box 18)
      - Nance, Donald (Box 18)
      - Narver, John (Box 18)
      - Narver, Ursel (Box 18)
      - North, William (Box 18)
      - Oakes, Charles Ernest (Box 18)
      - Odell, Norman (Box 18)
      - Orell, Bernard (Box 18)
      - Ossey, B.A. (Box 18)
      - Ott, Walter (Box 18)
      - Palmer, Claude (Box 18)
      - Pape, Dean (Box 18)
      - Paulson, Norris (Box 18)
      - Penrose, George (Box 18)
      - Perry, Grant W. (Box 18)
      - Pierson, Lenn (Box 18)
      - Pierce, Robert (Box 18)
      - Pihas, John (Box 18)
      - Pine, W.D. (Box 18)
      - Pittam, William (Box 18)
      - Poling, Dan (Box 18)
      - Powell, George "Gap" (Box 18)
      - Powell, James (Box 18)
      - Powell, Virgil A.A. (Box 18)
      - Prahl, Charles (Box 18)
      - Proppe, William (Box 18)
      - Proudfit, Arthur (Box 18)
      - Prusinski, Robert (Box 18)
      - Ramsey, Frank (Box 18)
      - Ramsey, Fred (Box 18)
      - Rau, Robert (Box 18)
      - Rave, W.J. (Box 18)
      - Reed, Claude (Box 18)
      - Reed, Robin (Box 18)
      - Reed, Steve and Mary (Box 18)
      - Reynolds, Charles (Box 18)
      - Reynolds, Jay (Box 18)
      - Reynolds, Jean Hall (Box 18)
      - Rice, Edna (Box 18)
      - Rieke, Forrest and Mary (Box 18)
      - Riley, Earl (Box 18)
      - Robertson, Bill (Ropesole) (Box 18)
      - Rocha, Ephriam (Box 18)
      - Rodgers, Fred (Box 18)
      - Roe, Robert (Box 18)
      - Rogers, Emsley (Box 18)
      - Roll, Leslie (Box 18)
      - Root, Robert (Box 18)
      - Roth, Vincent (Box 18)
      - Ruegg, Robert (Box 18)
      - Rumbaugh, Harold (Box 18)
      - Rushing, Robert (Box 18)
      - Rutherford, Harry (Box 18)
      - Salishan (Box 18)
      - Salser, Carl W. (Box 18)
      - Sabin, Lynn (Box 18)
      - Sarna, S.S. (Box 18)
      - Saubert, Jean (Box 18)
      - Saylor, Ralph (Box 18)
      - Schissler, Paul (Box 18)
      - Schmidt, Adolph (Box 18)
      - Schoth, Harry (Box 18)
      - Schulein, Joesph (Box 18)
      - Schmulmerich, Wes (Box 18)
      - Scott, George (Box 18)
      - Sears, Ernest (Box 18)
      - Sears, Vic (Box 18)
      - Seiler, Don (Box 18)
      - Severson, Win (Box 18)
      - Sewell, Elain Kollins (Box 18)
      - Shaw, Clayton (Box 18)
      - Shideler, Fred (Box 18)
      - Shy, G. Milton (Box 18)
      - Sidor, Ed (Box 18)
      - Siegrist, Ron (Box 18)
      - Slater, Jack (Box 18)
      - Slinger, Robert (Box 18)
      - Smith, Lawrence (Box 18)
      - Sowers, Philip (Box 18)
      - Spaur, George (Box 18)
      - Stanley, Edwin (Box 18)
      - Starker, Thurman (Box 18)
      - Starr, Eugene (Box 18)
      - Strand, A.L. (Box 18)
      - Swan, L.L. (Box 18)
      - Swan, Robert G. (Box 18)
      - Sweeney, Pat (Box 18)
      - Tartar, Herman Vance (Box 18)
      - Taylor, Ray (Box 18)
      - Thelan, Marilyn (Stout) (Box 18)
      - Thieleman, R.H. (Box 18)
      - Thomas, Dale (Box 18)
      - Thompson, Robert (Box 18)
      - Torrey, Dan (Box 18)
      - Turner, Art (Box 18)
      - Turner, Hester (Box 18)
      - Tuthill, Lewis (Box 18)
      - Unidentified Photos (Box 18)
      - Valley, Wayne (Box 18)
      - Valenti, Paul (Box 18)
      - Vincent, George (Box 18)
      - Vinyard, Harold (Box 18)
      - Wallace, Albert (Box 18)
      - Wardell, George (Box 18)
      - Warren, Charles (Box 18)
      - Wallace, Edwin (Box 18)
      - Wann, Harry (Box 18)
      - Weartherford, Mark (Box 18)
      - Weber, B.W. (Box 18)
      - Wei, C.K. Jui (Box 18)
      - Weimar, Virginia (Box 18)
      - Wellman, Harry (Box 18)
      - Wenstrom, Chuck (Box 18)
      - Werner, Richard (Box 18)
      - West, Flavius (Box 18)
      - White, George (Box 18)
      - White, Robert (Box 18)
      - Whiteside, Harold (Box 18)
      - Wiesner, Sue (Box 18)
      - Wilbur, Marvin (Box 18)
      - Williamson, Clyde (Box 18)
      - Wilkinson, Ron (Box 18)
      - Withycombe, James (Box 18)
      - Wood, Lavelle (Box 18)
      - Woodford, William (Box 18)
      - Yadon, John (Box 18)
      - Yerian, Ted (Box 18)
      - Young, Roy (Box 18)
      - Zarosinski, Donald (Box 18)
    - Letters to the Editor, 1987-1999; 10 folders (Box 14)
    - Letters to the Editor - Oregon Trail Project, 1992; 7 folders (Box 14)
    - General Correspondence, 1952-1994; 3 folders (Box 14)
    - Photo Contest, 1973-1974 (Box 14)
    - Press Releases, 1964-1982 (Box 14)
    - Costs, 1962-1984; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Student Publications Committee, 1976 (Box 14)
    - Tom Bennett Manuscripts for World War II Stories, 1991 (Box 14)
    - Sample mock-up and galley proof, 1964 (Box 1)
      For the September/October issue.
    - "The House the Thrill Kids Built" manuscript by Alex Petersen, 2000 (Box 14)
    - Oregon Stater Article Files, 1987-1998
      Materials generated and collection by the Oregon Stater staff in the course of writing and editing the alumni magazine. The files include transcripts of interviews, article drafts, correspondence, newspaper clippings, photographs, press releases, and publications. Most of the files are for a particular magazine issue; others are for specific topics.
      - February 1988 issue (Box 18)
      - October 1988 issue (Box 18)
      - December 1988 issue (Box 18)
      - September 1989 issue (Box 18)
      - December 1989 issue (Box 18)
      - September 1990 issue (Box 18)
      - February 1991 issue (World War II) (Box 18)
      - April 1991 issue (Box 18)
      - June 1991 issue (Box 18)
      - September 1991 issue (Box 18)
      - October 1991 issue (Box 18)
      - April 1992 issue (Box 18)
      - April 1994 issue (Box 18)
      - December 1994 issue (Box 18)
      - February 1995 issue (Box 18)
      - April 1995 issue (Box 18)
      - June 1995 issue (Box 18)
      - September 1995 issue (Box 18)
      - OSU connections with the U.S. Civil War (1861-1865), 1994 (Box 18)
      - Draft articles from Tom Bennett, 1995-1996 (Box 18)
      - History of the Beaver yearbook, 1994 (Box 18)
      - Awards and Alumni Fellows (J.W. "Bud" Forrester), 1991 (Box 18)
      - History of the OSU Alumni Association, 1990 (Box 18)
      - William Jasper Kerr, 1995 (Box 19)
      - Various Interviews, 1990 (Box 19)
      - General, 1987-1998; 3 folders (Box 19)
  - OSU Scope, 1966-1971; Series II; 2 folders (Box 19)
    Series II consists of correspondence, memos, notes, and mock-ups pertaining to this quarterly newsletter for alumni and friends of OSU that was published by the Department of Information.
  - Orange and Black, 1938; Series III (Box 15)
    Four copies of the Orange and Black, a pictorial history of Oregon State College published by the Alumni Association in commemoration of the 70th anniversary of OSC. Edited by Richard Charles (Dick) Gearhart, it includes a narrative history and photographs of the campus, student activities and traditions, athletics, and living organizations. According to the title-page inscription, it is "A record of the first seventy years in the life of Oregon State College -- the illustrated story of her growth to the 'major industry in the State', complete with the changing life and activity of her students and alumni." Promotional materials for the Orange and Black are available in the Memorabilia Collection. The E.T. Reed Papers include materials pertaining to a substantial revision of the publication that Reed worked on from 1938 until his death; it was never published. Additional information about the preparation, publication, and distribution is available in the microfilmed records (Series XVIII. General Files). The Orange and Black is available online.
  - Alumni Directories, 1910-2005; Series IV
    Series IV consists of alumni directories published by the Association. During the 1940s and 1950s, alumni directories were published as part of the Oregon Stater alumni magazine. Other lists of alumni are available in Subgroup 1 (Series III. Alumni Register) and Subgroup 2 (Series XVI. List of Alumni).
    - 1910 (Box 19)
    - 1913, 3 copies (Box 19)
    - 1917, 3 copies (Box 19)
    - 1922 (Box 19)
    - 1925, 3 copies (Box 19)
    - Class of 1965, 1967 (Box 19)
    - 2005 (Box 19)
      Includes published volume and CD with electronic version of alumni membership. The published directory includes lists by name, school (or college), class year, and current location.
- Microfilmed Records, 1888-1964; Subgroup 4
  Subgroup 4 consists of records that were microfilmed in 1969. There are no series II, IX, X, or XVII in this subgroup. Some of the documents on microfilm are available in paper form in other subgroups. The records document the full range of Association activities including class reunions and special events, publications, and fundraising. Most of the microfilm does not include folder targets.
  - Class Reunion Files, 1891-1959; Series I
    - 1891-1906 (Reel 1)
    - 1907-1926 (Reel 2)
    - 1926-1959 (Reel 3)
  - Reunion Weekends, 1939-1942; Series III (Reel 3)
  - Class Financial Records, 1924-1934; Series IV (Reel 3)
  - Reunion Lists, 1923-1925; Series V (Reel 3)
  - Reunion Letters, 1905; Series VI (Reel 3)
  - Alumni Mailing List, 1935; Series VII (Reel 4)
  - Reunion Banquets, 1916-1946; Series VIII (Reel 4)
  - Alumni Association, 1942; Series XI (Reel 4)
  - Class Lists, 1926-1945; Series XII (Reel 4)
  - Mailing Lists of Alumni, 1940-1941; Series XIII (Reel 4)
  - Golden Jubilee Lists and Correspondence, 1888-1964; Series XIV (Reel 4)